KONSTANTIN "KONSTA" KOMOVITS

JUNIOR FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER IT SPECIALIST





+358 40 142 0221



konsta.2106@gmail.com



Runkokatu 7 D 10, 33340 Tampere



https://www.linkedin.com/in/konstantin-komovits/

SKILLS

- APIs (API Design, OAS, Swagger, Postman)
- Back End (NodeJS, NPM)
- Front End (JS, HTML, CSS, React, Next)
- Databases (MongoDB, CosmosDB)
- Azure Cloud
- Integrations
- Data Engineering
- Languages: Finnish, English, Russian



EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Tampere University of Applied Sciences

2010 - 2015

FULLSTACK WEB DEVELOPER

Tampere University of Applied Sciences 2019-2020

PROFILE

I am a passionate IT specialist with a couple of years of experience in APIs, integrations, data flows, and Azure Cloud components. A big desire to continue developing my professional skills and grow in my career as an IT expert. Next, I am interested in continuing to develop my Azure Cloud knowledge as a developer and, in the future, as an architect.

EXPERIENCE

API DESIGNER

Platform of Trust Oy 2020 - Present

- API Design and Developer Experience (OAS, guides, developer portal, Postman collections)
- Designing integrations and data flows
- Coordinating partners for building integration connectors
- Designing and implementing data storage solutions in Azure Cloud

CAR DETAILER

Mje-Fix Oy 2016-2020

Car detailing